http://www.isr.ch/international-school-rheintal-privacy-policy/

Academic Programs
International Baccalaureate (IB)
Primary Years Program (IB PYP)
Middle Years Program (IB MYP)
Diploma Program (IB DP)
Academic Programs
International Baccalaureate (IB)
Primary Years Program (IB PYP)
Middle Years Program (IB MYP)
Diploma Program (IB DP)
International School Rheintal Privacy Policy
The International School Rheintal (ISR) respects the privacy of every individual who visits our website. To underscore our commitment to protecting your personal information, this privacy policy outlines what information we may collect, how we collect it and how that information is used. Please note that this policy may be amended in the future to reflect changes in law or ISR policies. You are advised to visit this policy periodically to stay up to date with changes or amendments. Personal data is collected for and on behalf of ISR. This pertains to both information collected in analogue form (forms, documents, in writing) and through technological means, such as the ISR website, information systems and email.
What is personal data?
Personal data is the information that identifies you, such as your name, address, email, photo or postal address. Your personal data is controlled by Verein International School Rheintal, Liechtenstein – St. Gallen – Vorarlberg, an organization registered in Switzerland and whose registered office is located at Aeulistrasse 10, 9470 Buchs, SG.
Collection of data
ISR is a leading educational institution and personal data supplied by you will only be used to aid ISR in fulfilling its educational vision and mission goals. We collect and use personal data to provide you with required services which may include: identifying authorized website users for password areas, responding to or fulfilling a request; processing admissions applications and records; maintaining school and administrative data records; processing of financial-related transactions and conducting anonymous statistical analysis of the ISR website and user structure.
ISR, as an educational institution, may also use your personal data to inform you via email or post about our educational activities and services, unless you have expressly notified ISR that you do not to wish to receive such information.
ISR will not rent, trade, transfer or sell your personal data to third-parties, and will only share data with third-parties for products or services necessary to assist ISR in meeting its organisational objectives. All third-party suppliers are obliged to respect and safeguard the confidentiality and security of your data and will not use your data for any other purposes than what we have agreed with them.
If the personal data that you have provided is incorrect or has changed since you submitted it, we request that you please contact us in writing (or email with the necessary changes) at dataprotection@isr.ch.
Cookies
Cookies which are small pieces of information sent from our website to your computer or mobile device and that are stored on your device’s hard drive. Cookies allow us to gather useful information such as the number of visitors to our site, which pages they have been visiting and other technical information that allows us to improve our services.
ISR uses cookies to track our online traffic flow, to provide a better user experience for social and multi-media and to personalize information in online forms. As a website user, you can set your web browser to accept all cookies, to notify you when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. Please note that the information supplied by cookies helps ISR to provide you with a better user experience and that by not accepting cookies, this may affect your ability to access certain parts of our website.
Information you share
ISR’s online services include the ability to share information with others. Remember that when you enter personal data in the “public” area of the password protected community that data is visible for all users who have been approved and can access the password-protected area.
Analytics
We use website statistic packages such as Google Analytics to analyse trends in how our website is accessed and utilised. Information monitored includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, geographic location of visitors (country, city), browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, time spent on pages, and keywords used to find our site via search engines. This information is anonymous and cannot be directly linked to individual users. We may use it to identify high-use or low-use areas of the site, pinpoint problem areas of the site, analyse broad demographic trends in our visitors and make decisions about how to make it easier for people to find and navigate our website.
If you don’t want Analytics to be used in your browser, you can install the Google Analytics browser add-on. More information about the ways in which Google Analytics collects and processes personal data can be found here: https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners.
Links
This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.
Contact
If you wish to raise a complaint or require further information on how we have handled your personal data, you can contact our Data Protection Team at dataprotection@isr.ch
If you are not satisfied with our response, or believe we are processing your personal data not in accordance with the law you can refer to the supervisory authority in Switzerland:
Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner (FDPIC)
Feldeggweg 1
CH- 3003 Berne
Switzerland
Please contact me... If you have any questions, we are happy to assist you. Just leave your contact details and we will get back to you as soon as possible.
CONTACT
International School Rheintal
Aeulistrasse 10
9470 Buchs
Switzerland
Tel: +41 81 750 63 00
Fax +41 81 750 63 01
office@isr.ch
FÜRSTENTUM LIECHTENSTEINGefördert durch Finanzhilfen des Fürstentums Liechtenstein
KANTON ST.GALLENStandortförderung
EUROPÄISCHE UNIONEuropäischer Fonds für Regionale Entwicklung
PARTNER COMPANIES
SUPPORTERS
Sichtbar AG, LI-Triesen
created and designed by kunstwort
